<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>Whisper</title>
  <lyrics>[V1]
 1) Your love and affection is sweeter than honey;
 Your Name is an ointment most fragrant of all
 Refreshing and soothing for me to discover;
 Romantic and lovely, desire of all.

[V2]
 2) You wandered alone among sad human beings,
 You spoke words of grace sharing Your heart of love,
 You flowed a true balm that heals all that does ail us.
 Despite our poor lack, You came far from above.

[V3]
 3) Your face like a flint, You held true to Your mission;
 Jerusalem’s pathway You fearlessly sought.
 Fulfilling God’s will, You delighted to do it.
 Forsaken by God, Your blood ran from the cross.

[V4]
 4) You gave all for others, in darkness so hidden;
 Your work quite completed, You lay in the grave;
 The One who was honored was left alone quickly
 Asleep in a tomb in a desolate cave.

[V5]
 5) All hope had just vanished and prospects departed;
 The daylight had faded, the earth filled with gloom.
 Oh Lord of my life, why so quickly You perished?
 Oh Lord of my love, You departed too soon.

[V6]
 6) Appearing in glory, You were manifested;
 The third day Your kindness and love was made known,
 The life of res’rrection flows out through Your loving;
 The pow'r of ascension, my reality.

[V7]
 7) When I gaze upon You, then all else does vanish;
 Your sweetness we taste and the world disappears.
 I bathe in Your love and I sense Your dear sweetness;
 My heart and my soul give to You all my years.</lyrics>
  <author>Titus Chu</author>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <hymn_number>SHL 49</hymn_number>
  <presentation></presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka></aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <linked_songs/>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <backgrounds resize="screen" keep_aspect="false" link="false" background_as_text="false"/>
</song>