<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>Deep in the Garden</title>
  <author>Nat Jordan</author>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <presentation></presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka></aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <lyrics>[v1]
 Deep in the garden, where fruit’s always ripe -
 A buffet for the ages, a vegan’s delight -
 Only one tree with which they weren’t to wrangle,
 Only one grapefruit they were to let dangle.
 Yet for all their riches, and privilege resplendent,
 When the snake said eat freely - they chose independence.
 Their innocence shattered, death melted their glow -
 They chose to know, they chose to know.
[v2]
 Now you sit in Eden, hoping for more,
 An eye on the life tree, and eye on the door.
 The food, it’s consistent, but you think it fraud,
 And burn to have freedom, and burn to be gods.
 And though it’s forbidden, only one tree
 Can sever dependence, can give you that key.
 A breath of temptation, a nudge and you fold -
 You choose to know, you choose to know.
[v3]
 With knowledge inside you, you think you can see.
 You counsel your brethern and point out their deeds.
 Wielding the Bible, deciphering right,
 Pointing and wielding, you kill all the life.
 And that’s when God asks you, where have you run,
 And if you are lucky, you’ll see what you’ve done.
 Starved in your tower, your ivory throne -
 You chose to know, you chose to know.
[v4]
 Then quietly exit, acknowledge defeat.
 Forget exegesis, admit you’re weak.
 Remember your stomach, unfed for so long,
 Collapse in the Bible, where hungry belong.
 Declare your dependence, a reverse July 4,
 And sample the fruit of the tree you ignored.
 Don’t cast out your knowledge, but use it to sow -
 And choose to grow, and choose to grow
 And choose to grow, and choose to grow.
</lyrics></song>