<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>Here To Stay</title>
  <author>Anna Schulz</author>
  <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
  <presentation>V1 C V2 C B</presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka>60</aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <lyrics>[V1]
.    G                                C          D
 The sun goes down, the stars up, the day closes down.
.  G          Em         C                   D
 I long for a friend, to watch twilight with me.
.    C           D       G              C
 I reflect on my day, on how it went my way,
.      G              D      C                    D       G
 But I really want, I really want a friend that’s here to stay.||
;.
 The wind dies down, the world hushed, the sky full of peace.
 I whisper to You as I lie down to sleep.  
 My whole heart yearns to rest, upon my Savior’s breast-
 But my heart cries out, wonders still, where Jesus was today.

[C]
.  C         G          C               G
 I love You, Lord, Your Spirit lives in me.
.C           G           Am          D
 Then why, O Lord, don’t I depend on Thee?
.           C        D            G                 C
 You’re the precious One, One who died and rose for me.
.      G                    D           C            D         C
 Yet I still don’t waste, I still don’t waste myself wholly on Thee.||
;.
 The world has its charms, its glories and gems,
 Trying to turn me away from You again.
 But draw me, dear Lord, keep me, Lord, seal my heart.
 Pursue me, Lord, and never let me from You depart.

[V2]
 The mountains high, the oceans show You’re beautiful.
 I thank You, dear Lord, for yearning after me.
 I long for sweet words, “Well done good, faithful slave!”
 Stay with me, live with me, for one long glorious day.||
;.
 I pray as I consider the things that I did,
 But cause me, dear Lord, to care for how I live.
 Lord, not foolish nor rich, nor wanting other things,
 But joyously and willingly living unto Thee.
---
[B]
.C          D         G         C
 Move in me Lord, for Your economy
.       G           D      C          D           G
 ‘Til I fully turn and wholly give my whole being unto Thee.
</lyrics></song>