<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>My Heart is Hungry, My Spirit doth Thirst</title>
  <author>Witness Lee</author>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <presentation>V1 C V2 C V3 C V4 C V5 C V6 C V7 C V8 C</presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka>132, 811</aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <lyrics>[V1]
.   G                   D7          G
 My heart is hungry, my spirit doth thirst;
.   Em      C             A7        D
 I come to Thee, Lord, to seek Thy supply;
.G          C            G
 All that I need is none other but Thee,
.  D7           G          D7     G
 Thou canst my hunger and thirst satisfy.

[C]
.G              D7     Em         B7
 Feed me, Lord Jesus, give me to drink,
. C           G                    D7
 Fill all my hunger, quench all my thirst;
. G                                        C
 Flood me with joy, be the strength of my life,
. G                   D7           G
 Fill all my hunger, quench all my thirst.

[V2]
 Thou art the food and the water of life,
 Thou canst revive me, my spirit upbear;
 I long to eat and to drink here of Thee,
 Thyself enjoy through my reading and prayer.

[V3]
 Thou art the Word with God’s fullness in Thee,
 Thou too the Spirit that God my life be;
 Thee in the Word I enjoy as my food,
 Thou as the Spirit art water to me.

[V4]
 Thou from the heavens as food camest down,
 Thou to be drink hast been smitten for me;
 Thou as the food, my exhaustless supply,
 Thou as the water, a stream unto me.

[V5]
 Thou in the Word art the Spirit and life,
 Thus by the Word I may feed upon Thee;
 Thou dost as Spirit in my spirit live,
 Thus I may drink in the spirit of Thee.

[V6]
 Now to enjoy Thee I come to Thy Word,
 On Thee to feed till my hunger is o’er.
 Now in my spirit I turn unto Thee,
 Of Thee to drink till I’m thirsty no more.

[V7]
 Feeding and drinking, Lord Jesus, of Thee,
 Feeding by reading, and drinking by prayer;
 Reading and praying, I eat and I drink,
 Praying and reading - Lord, Thou art my fare.

[V8]
 Here, O my Lord, may I feast upon Thee;
 Flood with Thy Spirit and fill by Thy Word;
 May, Lord, Thou be such a feast unto me
 As man hath never enjoyed nor e’er heard.
</lyrics></song>