<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>O Glorious Christ Savior Mine</title>
  <author></author>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <hymn_number></hymn_number>
  <presentation>V1 C V2 C V3 C V4 C V5 C V6 C V7 C E</presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka></aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <lyrics>[v1]
 1) O glorious Christ, Savior mine,
 Thou art truly radiance divine;
 God infinite, in eternity,
 Yet man in time, finite to be.
[c]
 Chorus  
 Oh! Christ, expression of God, the Great,
 Inexhaustible, rich, and sweet!
 God mingled with humanity
 Lives in me my all to be.
[v2]
 2) The fulness of God dwells in Thee;
 Thou dost manifest God’s glory;
 In flesh Thou hast redemption wrought;
 As Spirit, oneness with me sought.
[v3]
 3) All things of the Father are Thine;
 All Thou art in Spirit is mine;
 The Spirit makes Thee real to me,
 That Thou experienced might be.
[v4]
 4) The Spirit of life causes Thee
 By Thy Word to transfer to me.
 Thy Spirit touched, Thy word received,
 Thy life in me is thus conceived.
[v5]
 5) In spirit while gazing on Thee,
 As a glass reflecting Thy glory,
 Like to Thyself transformed I’ll be,
 That Thou might be expressed thru me.
[v6]
 6) In no other way could we be
 Sanctified and share Thy vict’ry;
 Thus only spiritual we’ll be
 And touch the life of glory.
[v7]
 7) Thy Spirit will me saturate Every part will God permeate,
 Deliv’ring me from the old man, With all saints building for His plan.
[E]
 1) O glorious Christ, Savior mine, Thou art truly radiance divine;
 God infinite, in eternity, Yet man in time, finite to be.
 Chorus  
 Oh! Christ, expression of God, the Great, Inexhaustible, rich, and sweet!
 God mingled with humanity Lives in me my all to be.
 2) The fulness of God dwells in Thee; Thou dost manifest God’s glory;
 In flesh Thou hast redemption wrought; As Spirit, oneness with me sought.
 3) All things of the Father are Thine; All Thou art in Spirit is mine;
 The Spirit makes Thee real to me, That Thou experienced might be.
 4) The Spirit of life causes Thee By Thy Word to transfer to me.
 Thy Spirit touched, Thy word received, Thy life in me is thus conceived.
 5) In spirit while gazing on Thee, As a glass reflecting Thy glory,
 Like to Thyself transformed I’ll be, That Thou might be expressed thru me.
 6) In no other way could we be Sanctified and share Thy vict’ry;
 Thus only spiritual we’ll be And touch the life of glory.
 7) Thy Spirit will me saturate Every part will God permeate,
 Deliv’ring me from the old man, With all saints building for His plan.</lyrics></song>