<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>If I Gained the World But Lost the Savior</title>
  <author>Anna Olander, tr. composite</author>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <presentation>V1 V2 V3 V4</presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka>84, 1079</aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <lyrics>[V1]
.Dm              C                   A#
 If I gained the world, but lost the Savior,
.Dm                 C            A# C
 Were my life worth living for a day?
.A#                C                   F   Dm
 Could my yearning heart find rest and comfort
.D#                                 C
 In the things that soon must pass away?||
.      F              Dm              F   Dm
 If I gained the world, but lost the Savior,
.          F       Dm                   F  C
 Would my gain be worth the lifelong strife?
.A#                C                 F    Dm
 Are all earthly pleasures worth comparing
.A#            C                    A# F
 For a moment with a Christ-filled life?
[V2]
.Dm                C               A#
 Had I wealth and love in fullest measure,
.Dm            C                  A# C
 And a name revered both far and near,
.A#             C               F   Dm
 Yet no hope beyond, no harbor waiting,
.D#                                     C
 Where my storm-tossed vessel I could steer.||
.      F              Dm              F   Dm
 If I gained the world, but lost the Savior,
.       F         Dm                 F C
 Who endured the cross and died for me,
.A#                  C              F     Dm
 Could then all the world afford a refuge,
.A#             C                 A# F
 Whither, in my anguish, I might flee?
-!!
 
[V3]
.Dm            C                A#
 Oh what emptiness without the Savior
.Dm                 C            A# C
 'Mid the sins and sorrows here below!
.A#         C               F   Dm
 And eternity, how dark without Him!
.D#                                C
 Only night and tears and endless woe!||
.             F          Dm             F   Dm
 What, though I might live without the Savior,
.        F         Dm             F  C
 When I come to die, how would it be?
.A#               C                 F   Dm
 Oh, to face the valley's gloom without Him!
.A#              C          A# F
 And without Him all eternity!
[V4]
.Dm             C             A#
 Oh the joy of having all in Jesus!
.Dm                C              A# C
 What a balm the broken heart to heal!
.A#               C                  F   Dm
 Ne'er a sin so great, but He'll forgive it,
.D#                             C
 Nor a sorrow that He does not feel!||
.      F        Dm          F   Dm
 If I have but Jesus, only Jesus,
.        F         Dm             F  C
 Nothing else in all the world beside,
.A#              C               F    Dm
 Oh, then everything is mine in Jesus.
.A#                C               A# F
 For my needs and more He will provide.</lyrics>
  <hymn_number></hymn_number></song>