<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
  <title>Sons</title>
  <author>John N. Darby</author>
  <copyright></copyright>
  <hymn_number>SHL 27</hymn_number>
  <presentation></presentation>
  <ccli></ccli>
  <capo print="false"></capo>
  <key></key>
  <aka></aka>
  <key_line></key_line>
  <user1></user1>
  <user2></user2>
  <user3></user3>
  <theme></theme>
  <tempo></tempo>
  <time_sig></time_sig>
  <lyrics>[v1]
 1) Father, Thy name our souls would bless,
 As children taught by grace,
 Lift up our hearts in righteousness,
 And joy before Thy face.
[v2]
 2) Sweet is the confidence Thou giv’st,
 Though high above our praise;
 Our hearts resort to where Thou liv’st
 In heav’ns unclouded rays.
[v3]
 3) There in the purpose of Thy love,
 Our place is now prepared,
 As sons with Him who is above,
 Who all our sorrows shared.
[v4]
 4) Eternal ages shall declare
 The riches of Thy grace,
 To those who with Thy Son shall share
 A son’s eternal place.
[v5]
 5) Absent as yet, we rest in hope,
 Treading the desert path,
 Waiting for Him who takes us up
 Beyond the pow’r of death.
[v6]
 6) We joy in Thee, Thy holy love
 Our endless portion be,
 Like Thine own Son, with Him above,
 In brightest heav’nly bliss.
[v7]
 7) O Holy Father, keep us here
 In that blest name of love,
 Walking before Thee without fear,
 Till all be joy above.
[E]
 1) Father, Thy name our souls would bless, As children taught by grace,
 Lift up our hearts in righteousness, And joy before Thy face.
 2) Sweet is the confidence Thou giv’st, Though high above our praise;
 Our hearts resort to where Thou liv’st In heav’ns unclouded rays.
 3) There in the purpose of Thy love, Our place is now prepared,
 As sons with Him who is above, Who all our sorrows shared.
 4) Eternal ages shall declare The riches of Thy grace,
 To those who with Thy Son shall share A son’s eternal place.
 5) Absent as yet, we rest in hope, Treading the desert path,
 Waiting for Him who takes us up Beyond the pow’r of death.
 6) We joy in Thee, Thy holy love Our endless portion be,
 Like Thine own Son, with Him above, In brightest heav’nly bliss.
 7) O Holy Father, keep us here In that blest name of love,
 Walking before Thee without fear, Till all be joy above.</lyrics>
  <linked_songs/>
  <backgrounds resize="screen" keep_aspect="false" link="false" background_as_text="false"/>
</song>